Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
1972-1997
Gerard Designs.
18.5 linear ft.
Collection consists of drawings of molds created by Gerard Designs for various companies in the plastics and other industries. Most drawings contain initials of Robert McGee.
2651121
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings consists of drawings of molds created by Gerard Designs for various companies in the plastics and other industries, including Parker Brothers, Monsanto, and General Electric. Most drawings contain initials of Robert McGee. See Index to Companies at the end of this finding aid for a complete alphabetical list.
Drawings are in relatively good condition; however, many are faded where exposed to light and acidic materials for long periods of time.
Arrangement of the Collection
Arranged by drawing number, which is also roughly chronological.
Related Material
has numerous holdings in the areas of plastics and industrial design. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Industrial Design; Plastics; McGee, Robert.; General Electric Company.; Gerard Designs -- Archives.; Milton Bradley Company.; Monsanto Company.; Parker Brothers, inc.; Nypro (UK) Limited.; Plastics in packaging.; Plastics industry and trade.; Plastics -- Molds.; Drawings (visual works); Molds (shaping tools)
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from National Plastics Center and Museum, 11/06/2008.
Inventory
- Drawings
  - #1176: 8 cavity cuvette base mold, 1972 (Box 1)
  - #1182: 16 cavity shave cream spout mold, 1972 (Box 1)
  - #1184: Single cavity paint container cover mold, 1972 (Box 1)
  - #1201: Safe-tag, 1972; made for Synthetic Products (Box 1)
  - #1205: Single cavity chair back insert mold design, 1972; made for Stan-Cast (Box 1)
  - #1211: 4-cavity soap dish mold, 1972; made for J&R Mold Co. (Box 1)
  - #1214: Unidentified, 1972 (Box 1)
  - #1215: insulators, 1972; made for SPMCO (Box 1)
  - #1219: 1-cavity be-cu & alum. core, 1972; made for Stan-Cast (Box 1)
  - #1232: 2 cavity picture guard mold, 1972; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 1)
  - #1241: haydon switch & instrument housing, 1972; made for Phillips MFG. Co. Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1244: single drawer jewelry chest, 1972; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 1)
  - #1246: three drawer jewelry cheste mold, 1972; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 1)
  - #1253: single cavity cover mold, 1972 (Box 1)
  - #1254: 1-cavity be. cu. cavity & alum. core 396-11 cocktail table, 1972; made for Stan-Cast, Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1255: 1-cav.be.-cu. cavity & alum. core 396-12 sq. comm. door, 1972; made for Stan-Cast, Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1257: 1 cavity mold room for 4 cavities single cell, 1972; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1258: 1-cavity be.-cu. cav. & alum. core 36" console door #396-09, 1972; made for Stan-Cast, Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1259: stationary door 1-be.-cu. cav & alum core hex commode #396-32, 1972; made for Stan-Cast, Inc. (Box 1)
  - #1262: single cavity back panel mold, 1972; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 1)
  - #1265: 2 cavity mold sub search back control panel, 1972; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1266: 4 cavity box mold solo tair (cover & bottom), 1973; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1267: 4 cavity grid mold solo tair (front & back) grid, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 2)
  - #1269: 6 cavity high chair mold, 2 cav. backs, 4 cav. arms, 1973; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1272: 8 cavity threaded cap mold, 1973; made for Monsanto Company, Packaging Division (Box 2)
  - #1277: 2 vacity mold for item 4370 on target turntable, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 2)
  - #1278: single cavity base mold for item 4320, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 2)
  - #1279: 2 cavity mold 1-knob 1-base for storage unit, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 2)
  - #1280: 2 cavity top & bottom shell mold, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 2)
  - #1283: Unidentified, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 2)
  - #1284: 1 cavity mold for aux. water meter cover, 1973; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 2)
  - #1291: 8 cavity omnimeter mold, 1973; made for J&R Mold Co. (Box 2)
  - #1292: Unidentified, 1973; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 2)
  - #1295: motor and chain cover, 1972; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1297: 4 cavity mold lens cup, 1973; made for Crown Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1299: 4 cavity mold super market divider, 1973; made for Crown Tool & Die Co. (Box 2)
  - #1302: 2-cavity turntable tray, 1973; made for Sterilite Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1303: 4 cavity family mold, 1973; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1304: 1-cavity 15" laundry basket mold, 1973; made for Sterilite Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1305: 2-cavity 6/8 track storage box mold, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1306: 4 cavity mold base, 1973; made for Regent Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1307: 4 cavity mold bell jar, 1973; made for Regent Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1308: 18 cavity mold optical hinge and cap, 1973; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1313: 32 cavity mold side bumper sleeve, 1973; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1314: 32 cavity mold bumper pool "o" ring, 1973; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1315: sin. cavity slat mold, 1973; made for The Lakso Co., Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1316: 4 cavity mold goalie stick, 1973; made for Mold & Pattern Co. (Box 3)
  - #1317: 3-cavity pre-mix chamber mold, 1973; made for Union Tool & Mold Co. (Box 3)
  - #1322: single cavity be.-cu. cavity & alum. core bed splate, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1328: 1-cavity mold can opener jar wrench, 1973; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 3)
  - #1329: 1 cavity mold can opener handle, 1973; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 3)
  - #1337: 6-cavity plastic hub mold, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 3)
  - #1338: hair brush block, 1973; made for E. I. du Pont de Nemours (Box 3)
  - #1342: 1 cavity mold 10" hanging flower pot, 1973; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 3)
  - #1345: 2-cavity mold for impeller parts, 1973; made for Mold & Pattern Co. (Box 3)
  - #1350: single cavity chair back mold, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 3)
  - #1351: 2 cavity mold, 1973; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 4)
  - #1352: 2 cavity letter wheel mold, 1973; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 4)
  - #1358: 24 cavity .15 dram snap cap mold, 1973; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 4)
  - #1359: 8 cavity mold 1/2 gallon picnic jug, 1973; made for Amoco Chemicals Corp., Tool Engineering Division (Box 4)
  - #1360: 4 cavity mold 1 gallon picnic jug, 1973; made for Amoco Chemicals Corp., Tool Engineering Division (Box 4)
  - #1361: single cavity doar foam mold, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1362: yarn tray, 1973; made for Doyle Works (Box 4)
  - #1364: 2 cavity mold lamp shade, 1973; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1365: 2 cavity mold lamp top, 1973; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1367: 2 cavity handle mold, 1973; made for Mapco Tool (Box 4)
  - #1369: 1 cavity 513 cuvette body mold, 1973; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1370: single cavity mold PCO2 end tank, 1973; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1371: single cavity mold PO2 end tank, 1973; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1375: 8 cavity mold, 1973; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 4)
  - #1384: refill holder 14", 16", 18", 1973; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 4)
  - #1401: 8 cavity end bracket, 1973; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 4)
  - #1408: single cavity 14x25 door foam mold, 1973; 2 folders; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 4)
  - #1410: 4 cavity mold A0-10 handle, 1973; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 5)
  - #1411: 2 cavity mold fast back guard, 1973; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 5)
  - #1412: 4 cavity cuvette base mold, 1973; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1419: single cavity platter mold, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1421: 4 cavity mold can opener jar wrench, 1973; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 5)
  - #1426: preliminary water layout cuvette core, 1973; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1427: 2 cavity box & cover mold, 1973; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 5)
  - #1428: single cavity cutting board, 1973; made for Family Products (Box 5)
  - #1431: 4 cavity panel mold, 1973; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 5)
  - #1432: 8 cavity knob mold, 1973; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 5)
  - #1433: 1 cavity mold pivot-cover, 1973 (Box 5)
  - #1435: underground terminal box, 1973; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co., Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1439: roller derby 6 cavity injection mold, 1973; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 5)
  - #1440: single cavity overlay, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1441: single cavity cocktail door, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1442: single cavity casting door overlay, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1443: master layout for shuttle mold base, 1973; made for Barry Controls (Box 5)
  - #1446: 16 cavity injection mold for preform, 1973; made for Improved Machinery Co. (Box 5)
  - #1447: 3 cavity holster mold, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1450: 2 cavity mold bowmar battery cover, 1973; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 5)
  - #1452: single cavity chair back, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1453: handle cavities, 1973; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 5)
  - #1454: single cavity mold for hand tool, 1973; made for SPM Co. (Box 5)
  - #1456: 2 vacity mold for reflector, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 6)
  - #1457: 2 cavity mold for 180 lens, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 6)
  - #1458: 4 cavity end cover mold, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 6)
  - #1462: 4 cavity lens holder mold, 1973; made for J&R Mold Co. (Box 6)
  - #1464: single cavity mold for 8 track tape tray, 1973; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 6)
  - #1465: single cavity shuttle mold hmr. guide assembly, 1973; made for Collins Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1466: single cavity housing mold, 1974; made for Collins Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1471: 2 cavity video cassette, 1973; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 6)
  - #1474: 2 cavity housing mold, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 6)
  - #1475: 2 cavity escutcheon mold, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 6)
  - #1477: 2 cavity track mold, 1974; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1478: 8 cavity chip mold, 1974; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1480: isolator rail compression mold assembly, 1974; made for Barry Controls (Box 6)
  - #1481: 2 cavity frame mold, 1974; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1483: single cavity china door, 1974; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 6)
  - #1484: single cavity china door, 1974; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 6)
  - #1485: 2 cavity 5" rounsd speaker mold, 1974; made for Mapco Tool (Box 6)
  - #1494: 2 cavity cutter carrier, 1974; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 6)
  - #1495: single cavity housing mold, 1974; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 6)
  - #1496: since cavity mold for motor mount, 1974; made for Iona Manufacturing Co. (Box 6)
  - #1499: single cavity mold FCI base, 1974; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 6)
  - #1500: 32 cavity cam post, 1974; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 6)
  - #1501: 2 cavity mold pottin & boot, 1974; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 7)
  - #1502: 6 cavity hold down clip, 1974; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 7)
  - #1506: 2 cavity spout cap, 1974; made for SRC Medical Co. (Box 7)
  - #1510: single cavity mold bezel patent no. 165094, 1974; made for Leominster Die & Mold Co. (Box 7)
  - #1511: 2 cavity hair dryer, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 7)
  - #1512: single cavity #48700 base mold, 1974; 2 folders; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 7)
  - #1513: tube carrier pin conveyor, 1974 (Box 7)
  - #1515: 2 cavity quick over mold, 1974; made for Synthetic Products MFG Inc. (Box 7)
  - #1518: Unidentified, 1974; made for Doyle Works (Box 7)
  - #1520: 8 cavity figurene mold, 1974; made for Mapco Tool (Box 7)
  - #1521: single cavity mold, 1974; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 7)
  - #1523: 2 cavity trim plate mold, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 7)
  - #1525: turbo fan mold, 1974; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 7)
  - #1527: single cavity mold for platen drive gear, 1974; made for Westboro Plastic R&D Co. (Box 7)
  - #1528: 2 cavity hanger mold, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 7)
  - #1529: assembly-end plan, 1974; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 7)
  - #1533: adult toothbrush redesign #7 mold, 1974; made for E. I. du Pont de Nemours (Box 7)
  - #1536: Lockwood Plastics Co. knockout adaptor, 1974; made for Improved Machinery Co. (Box 7)
  - #1540: 2 cavity slide-"y" mold, 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 7)
  - #1544: 8 cavity injection mold life spinner, 1974; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 8)
  - #1545: inserts for 8 cavity bobbin mold, 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 8)
  - #1547: single cavity retainer mold, 1974; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 8)
  - #1548: single cavity sphere mold, 1974; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 8)
  - #1549: 4 cavity bumper mold, 1974; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 8)
  - #1550: single cavity cover mold, 1974; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 8)
  - #1552: 5 oz. cocktail glass, 1973; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 8)
  - #1553: 6 cavity pool cue handle mold, 1974; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 8)
  - #1560: 8 cavity mold bell, 1974; made for Bradford Novelty Co., Inc. (Box 8)
  - #1561: single cavity KCL junction plug mold, 1974; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 8)
  - #1562: single cavity mold KCL reservoir body, 1974; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 8)
  - #1563: single cavity mold KCL resevoir base, 1974; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 8)
  - #1564: cavity details, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 8)
  - #1565: 16 cavity master mold, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 8)
  - #1566: single cavity insulator mold, 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 8)
  - #1567: GE patent no 2G788130 cap, 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 8)
  - #1569: 2 cavity mold Vivacell II covers, 1974 (Box 8)
  - #1570: 2 cavity kit mold, 1972; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 8)
  - #1577: Unidentified, 1974 (Box 8)
  - #1580: octagon shaped compact, 1974; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 8)
  - #1581: Unidentified, 1974 (Box 8)
  - #1582: 2 cavity bar clip mold, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 8)
  - #1584: owner's game, 1974; made for Parker Brothers (Box 8)
  - #1587: 2 cavity mold for flag and/or cover, 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 8)
  - #1588: 8 cavity cord end mold (1 top half and 2 lower halves), 1974; made for General Electric Housewares Division (Box 8)
  - #1594, 1597, 1598: treasure hunt game assembly drawing, 1974; made for Parker Brothers (Box 9)
  - #1601: double cell cuvette assembly, 1974; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1603: 2 cavity insulated h.r. treasure hunt mold, 1974; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1605: 1 cavity mold battery section, 1974; made for Hardigg Industries Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1606: 2 cavity case & cover mold, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 9)
  - #1607: single and double spool tray, 1974; made for Doyle Works (Box 9)
  - #1608, 1609: 4 cavity mold 2 cell cuvette cover, 1974; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1611: 6 fluid ounce jar Noxzema skin cream, 1974; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 9)
  - #1612: 2 cavity body language base mold, 1974; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 9)
  - #1613: single cavity 16 quart split pail mold, 1975; made for Gotham Industries Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1614: 2 cavity mold Ritchie bearning compass (top and bottom case), 1974; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 9)
  - #1615: 2 cavity injection mold, 1974; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 9)
  - #1616: 8 cavity treasure hunt coin mold, 1974; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 9)
  - #1617: 2 cavity "E" block mold, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 9)
  - #1618: single cavity 18" table top mold, 1974; made for Gotham Industries Inc. (Box 9)
  - #1622: single cavity yoke mold, 1974; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 9)
  - #1634: single cavity culture dish mold, 1974; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 9)
  - #1635: single cavity insulator mold, 1974; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 9)
  - #1636: square compact Avon project, 1974; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 10)
  - #1637-1640: 4 cavity mold for 5" flower pot and dish, 1974; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 10)
  - #1642: 8 cavity mold for risk game box and cover, 1974; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 10)
  - #1643: single cavity housing mold, 1974; made for Beverly Pattern (Box 10)
  - #1645: 2 cavity foam mold insert & cover, 1974; made for Beverly Pattern (Box 10)
  - #1646, 1647: 24 cavity Nerf axle mold, hub and spacer, 1974; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 10)
  - #1649: 2 cavity buffy neck ring mold, 1974; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 10)
  - #1651: 4 cavity shuttle mold, 1975; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 10)
  - #1652: 2 cavity cover mold, 1974; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 10)
  - #1653: 2 cavity base mold, 1975; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 10)
  - #1659: 4 cavity mold for a cookie tray, 1975; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 10)
  - #1661: tube carrier pin conveyor, 1975; made for Doyle Works (Box 10)
  - #1671: standard double ejection mechanism, 1975; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 10)
  - #1674: 2 cavity foot pad mold, 1975; made for Hasbro Industry Inc. (Box 10)
  - #1675: 2 cavity mold universal side rail, 1975; made for Hasbro Industry Inc. (Box 10)
  - #1679: single cavity MVD insert for hand rail, 1975; made for Hasbro Industry Inc. (Box 10)
  - #1681: 7 cavity mold for tennis racket parts, 1975; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 10)
  - #1685: Unidentified, 1975 (Box 10)
  - #1686: 2 cavity mold impeller and bushing, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 10)
  - #1687: 3 cavity humidifier cap housing and roof mold, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 11)
  - #1689: 2 cavity family mold for base cover and base, 1975; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 11)
  - #1690: 2 cavity sphere mold for skor-mor, 1975; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 11)
  - #1693: single cavity century goal mold, 1975; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 11)
  - #1695: s-860 pin insulator, 1975; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 11)
  - #1698: 4 cavity Aramis box, 1975; made for Mark Technical Mold (Box 11)
  - #1699: 2 cavity microtiter mold, 1975; made for Data Packaging Corp. (Box 11)
  - #1700: single cavity game housing mold, 1975; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 11)
  - #1704: single cavity mold for five gallon container, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 11)
  - #1708: 16 cavity mold for swivel hook hanger, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 11)
  - #1709: Jimmy fund container, 1975; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 11)
  - #1710: single cavity mold for truss panel, 1975; made for Hardigg Industries Inc. (Box 11)
  - #1712: 4 cavity mold for corner cap, 1975; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 11)
  - #1714: 10 cavity mold for drip dry hanger, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 11)
  - #1719: single cavity mold for battery section, 1975; made for Hardigg Industries Inc. (Box 11)
  - #1721: 2 cavity mold top support, 1975; made for Victory Button Co. (Box 11)
  - #1725: single cavity mold battery section, 1975; made for Victory Button Co. (Box 11)
  - #1730: 8 cavity mold pocketscope parts, 1975; made for J&R Mold Co. (Box 12)
  - #1731: single cavity mold CTG shell, 1975; made for Danco Co. (Box 12)
  - #1732: 2 cavity mold housing, 1975; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 12)
  - #1733: 4 cavity base mold, 1975; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 12)
  - #1735: 4 cavity mold for paint bucket, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 12)
  - #1737: Ben Hur rack section, 1975; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 12)
  - #1744: 2 cavity mold dyino ticket cover, 1975; made for Phillips MFG (Box 12)
  - #1745: 8 cavity cover mold, 1975; made for L&L Mold Co. (Box 12)
  - #1746: 12 cavity mold ornament, 1975; made for Bradford Novelty Co. (Box 12)
  - #1751: single cavity 14x27 shelf, 1975; made forGotham Industries Inc. (Box 12)
  - #1752: 2 cavity container mold, 1975; made for Phillips MFG (Box 12)
  - #1755: single cavity large cover mold, 1975; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 12)
  - #1758: single cavity chassis mold, 1975; made for Dee & H. Tool Co. (Box 12)
  - #1760: single cavity mold P-9626 cover, 1975; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 12)
  - #1770: 6 cavity mold bug eye parts, 1975; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 12)
  - #1773: 2 cavity case mold, 1975; made for Data General Corp. (Box 12)
  - #1775-1777: 80 oz. decantor mold, 1975; made for Family Products (Box 12)
  - #1779: 4 cavity tumbler mold, 1975; made for Family Products (Box 13)
  - #1784: single cavity tote tray mold, 1975; made for Collins Tool & Die Co. (Box 13)
  - #1785-1787: 8 cavity mold Avon candid compact base, 1975; made for L&L Tool Co. (Box 13)
  - #1786: single cavity mold for battery section, 1975; made for Hardigg Industries Inc. (Box 13)
  - #1791: 2 cavity dome side mold, 1975; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 13)
  - #1795: single cavity clamp mold, 1975; made for Collings Tool & Die (Box 13)
  - #1796: single cavity mold 10 square terminal block, 1975; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 13)
  - #1808: single cavity mold "y" injection site cap, 1975; made for Collings Tool & Die (Box 13)
  - #1811: 2 cavity mold ball track and score dial, 1975; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 13)
  - #1814: 4 cavity mold cap, 1975; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 13)
  - #1815: 2 cavity family mold yoke and pivot, 1975; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 13)
  - #1820: 3 cavity mold 2-spool seat shaft 1-bearing, 1976; made for Data General Corp. (Box 13)
  - #1821: 3 cavity mold right and left ribbon guide and carriage, 1976; made for Data General Corp. (Box 13)
  - #1822: 4 cavity mold slide, flag, lever, 1976; made for Data General Corp. (Box 13)
  - #1824: 2 cavity mold P-10861 base, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 13)
  - #1826: single cavity truss mold, 1976; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 13)
  - #1827: 4 cavity room for 8 shell and bushings, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 13)
  - #1829: 2 cavity mold cover and push rod, 1976; made for Wachusett Molding Corp. (Box 13)
  - #1832: 16 cavity mold for 20 DR CRC vial, 1976; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 13)
  - #1834: 2 cavity mold console and housing, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 13)
  - #1839: 9 cavity (room for 12) mold guard and retainer strips, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 13)
  - #1841: 2 cavity mold D8227 polypro package, 1976; made for Creative Packaging (Box 14)
  - #1842: 6 cavity mold shell and brushing, 1976; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 14)
  - #1843: 2 cavity mold for 6" saucer, 1976; made for Lockwood Products (Box 14)
  - #1845: 8 cavity mold "y" injection site cap, 1976; made for Collins Tool & Die Co. (Box 14)